A Guide to the Laurance S. Rockefeller papers, Office and Home Files FA1353
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Projects and Properties, 1923-2009; 3; 76.78 Cubic Feet 177 containers
  - Real Estate and Investments, 1942-2009; 3_7
    - LSR - Quincy Adams Sloop, 1950 (Box 119, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Lightning Class Sloop "Squirrel", 1946 (Box 120, Folder 1)
    - LSR - The Courageous Syndicate, 1974 (Box 120, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Thermo Electron Corporation, 1967 (Box 120, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Disposition of Real Estate Owned by Ward M. Canaday on the Island of St. Croix to LSR, David Rockefeller, Harvard College and Bryn Mawr College, 1963 January 24 (Box 120, Folder 4)
    - LSR - East Fountain River Company, 1963-1984 (Box 120, Folder 5)
    - LSR - East Fountain River - East Fountain River Company and Fountain Valley Corp. to Sugar Land Associates - Closing, 1984 October 25 (Box 120, Folder 9, Box 122, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Yacht - "Dauntless", 1947-1948 (Box 120, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Loan Agreement - Bank of London and South America, Ltd., 1968 (Box 120, Folder 7)
      Refinancing expansion of hotel in British Virgin Islands.
    - LSR - Power of Attorney and Ratification - LSR and Jose G. Gonzales in Puerto Rico, 1957-1965 (Box 120, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Rockefeller Center - Leases (Box 122, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Automobile Club of New York, 1982 (Box 122, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Barton, Robert S. - Agreement re: Employment and Housing in Woodstock, 1969 (Box 122, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Guaranty of CMB Loans - Jackson Hole Preserve, Caneel Bay Plantation, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Gift to Corcoran Gallery of Art of Seven Colonel Bernt Balchen Watercolors, 1975 (Box 122, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Eastern Airlines - Stock Exchange Agreement, 1976 (Box 122, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Dana S. Creel - Agreement - Sale of Dried Shelled Corn, 1976 December 30 (Box 122, Folder 8)
    - LSR - Garrison Development Corp., 1966 (Box 122, Folder 9)
    - Rockefeller Associates Realty, 1990s (Box 122, Folder 10)
    - Clayton W. Frye (CWF) - Memos, 1991-2008 (Box 122, Folder 11)
    - Clayton W. Frye (CWF) - Chronological File, 2007 (Box 121, Folder 2)
    - Clayton W. Frye (CWF) - Rockefeller Family Offices, 2007-2008 (Box 123, Folder 1)
    - Clayton W. Frye (CWF) - Rockwood Hall, 1998 (Box 123, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust, 1999 (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust - General, 1999-2008 (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust - David A. Donath - Housing Option, 2002 (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust - Rockefeller Trust Company - Agency Agreement, 2004 (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Intervivos Trust - Sherman Howe Property, 2001-2003 (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - LSR - Disposition of Legal Documents, 2008 (Box 149, Folder 9)
    - LSR Fund - General, 1994-2000 (Box 144, Folder 9)
    - MSKCC - Marks Proposal - LSR Letter, 1998 (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - LSR Fund - Rockefeller Trust Company - Agreeements, 1994 (Box 149, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller, Mary French - Estate - Financial, 1997 (Box 149, Folder 11)
    - Open Space Institute (OSI) - Debt Reorganization, 1991-2006 (Box 144, Folder 10)
    - Rockefeller Trust Company, 1991-2004 (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - LSR - Gifts to Family and Family Trusts (Summary), 1989 August 31 (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Charitable Fund for Children, 1990-2002 (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Gifts to Children, 1989-2003 (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - Executors - General, 2004-2008 (Box 159, Folder 5)
    - LSR Estate - Executors - Meeting Minutes and Agenda, 2004-2008 (Box 159, Folder 6)
    - LSR Estate - Executors - Communications - Staff, 2004-2005 (Box 159, Folder 7)
    - LSR Estate - Milbank - Engagement Letter and Power of Attorney, 2004 July 19 (Box 159, Folder 8-9)
    - LSR Estate - Rockefeller Trust Company - Agency Agreement, 2004-2009 (Box 159, Folder 10)
    - LSR Estate - Biographies Trust (Box 159, Folder 11)
    - LSR Estate - Consultant - Douglas R. Horne, 2005 (Box 159, Folder 12)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - General, 2004-2009 (Box 159, Folder 13)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Appraisal - Cemetery Buffer, Pocantico, A-16 (Box 159, Folder 14)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Appraisals - Caribbean, 2004 (Box 159, Folder 15)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - British Virgin Islands Probate, 2005 (Box 166, Folder 1)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Vermont Probate, 2009 (Box 166, Folder 2)
    - LSR Estate - Real Estate - Woodstock Funding, 2007 (Box 166, Folder 3)
    - LSR Estate - General, 2004-2009 (Box 166, Folder 7)
    - LSR Estate - IRS Tax Issues, 2005-2008 (Box 166, Folder 8)
    - LSR Estate - Taxpayer ID, 2004-2005 (Box 166, Folder 9)
    - LSR Estate - Tax Issues - Estate Tax Closing, 2008 (Box 166, Folder 10)
    - LSR Estate - Transaction Statements, 2004-2009 (Box 166, Folder 11)
    - LSR Estate - Letters to Executors, 1987-2004 (Box 166, Folder 12)
  - Rockresorts, 1952-2003; 3_8
    - Rockresorts - General, 1960s-1994 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Transfer from CSX, 1985-1988 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - LSR - Arthur R. Taylor, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 9)
      Receipt and Release in Favor of LSR.
    - Rockresorts - Planning and Sale, 1978-1983 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Resolution to LSR, 1986 April (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Property and Personnel, 1985 April (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Hawaii Stock and Land Transactions - Sale to UAL, Inc., 1979; Bound volume (Box 85, Folder 4)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - Sale to UAL, Inc., 1978; Bound volume, 2 copies. (Box 86, Folder 1-2)
      Sale to United Air Lines, Inc.
    - Rockresorts - Speeches - Rockresorts - General, 1998-2001 (Box 82, Folder 15)
    - Rockresorts - Speeches - Woodstock Inn Dedication, 1969 November 23 (Box 86, Folder 3)
    - Rockresorts - Speeches - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel Dedication, 1968 September 21 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Speeches - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel Dedication, 1965 July 24 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel - General, 1983-2003 (Box 87, Folder 3-4, Box 88, Folder 1)
    - Rockresorts - Speeches - Little Dix Bay Dedication, 1964 January 18 (Box 87, Folder 5, Box 88, Folder 2)
    - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach Hotel Book, 2001 (Box 87, Folder 6)
      Presentation to LSR at Room 5600, photographs.
    - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach Hotel Opening, 1958-2003 (Box 89, Folder 1-2)
    - Rockresorts - Caneel Bay - General, 1956-2002 (Box 88, Folder 3)
    - LSR - Rockresorts, 1985-1986 (Box 128, Folder 2-4)
      Ownership agreements. Sale of Rockresorts, Inc. to CSX.
    - LSR - Rockresorts-CSX, 1986 (Box 128, Folder 5)
      Ownership agreements
    - Eastern Airlines and Dorado Beach Hotel, 1974; 1976 (Box 138, Folder 10)
    - LSR - Remarks - Rockresort Associates (Box 157, Folder 1)
    - Hawaii Properties - Mauna Kea Beach Hotel Corporation - Stock Gifts and Sales, 1952-1974 (Box 177, Folder 5)
    - Hawaii Properties - Documents and Correspondence, 1961-1983 (Box 177, Folder 6-7)
    - Hawaii Properties - Documents and Correspondence, 1961-1984 (Box 180, Folder 1-4)
    - Rockresorts - Hawaii - Land Use and Development, 1960s (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Rockresorts - Dorado Beach Properties, 1970 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Clippings, 1970 (Box 302, Folder 2)
    - Dorado Beach Hotel - Development Proposals, 1953 (Box 343, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Resorts - Mauna Kea, 1965-1978 (Box 403, Folder 12)
    - LSR - Resorts - Little Dix Bay - Stationary and Brochures, 1970s-1990s (Box 404, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Hawaii Properties (Box 404, Folder 3)
  - Valley Ranch, 1988-1995; 3_9
    - Valley Ranch: General, 1990-1995 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Valley Ranch - Landscaping, 1990-1994 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Valley Ranch - Sale, 1995 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - Valley Ranch - Water Rights, 1988-1994 (Box 49, Folder 8-9)
  - Virgin Islands, 1959-2009; 3_10
    - British Virgin Islands - Belonger Ceremony, 2003 September 26 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Sandy Cay - General, 1989-2000 (Box 54, Folder 1)
    - Sandy Cay - Island Resources Report - Resource Characterization, 2001 March (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - Sandy Cay - Management Plan, 2001 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - Property - Virgin Islands - Sandy Cay, 1999-2004 (Box 81, Folder 4)
    - Virgin Islands - Park (Box 81, Folder 5)
    - Virgin Islands - Bill Moody, 2002 (Box 81, Folder 6)
    - Kipahulu, Maui, Hawaii - Appraisals, 1995 (Box 81, Folder 6A)
    - LSR - Real Estate - Virgin Islands Properties - St. Croix, 1959-1966 (Box 110, Folder 11)
    - LSR - Real Estate - Virgin Islands Properties - St. Croix, 1963-1980 (Box 112, Folder 1)
    - LSR - Real Estate - Virgin Islands Properties - St. Croix - Real Estate Transactions, 1973 (Box 112, Folder 2)
    - LSR - Real Estate - Virgin Islands Properties - St. John, 1959-1977 (Box 112, Folder 3)
    - US Virgin Islands - Klumb, 1989-2008 (Box 134, Folder 1)
    - US Virgin Islands - Trigo, 1995-2008 (Box 134, Folder 2)
    - US Virgin Islands - National Park - Calabash Technologies, 2006 (Box 134, Folder 3)
    - US Virgin Islands - Caneel Bay, 1999-2008 (Box 134, Folder 4-6)
    - US Virgin Islands - General, 1972-2008 (Box 138, Folder 6)
    - US Virgin Islands - Caneel Bay - Retained Use Estate - General, 1986-2006 (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - US Virgin Islands - Caneel Bay - Retained Use Estate - LSR Letter, 1972-1989 (Box 144, Folder 8)
    - LSR Fund - Caneel Bay - Lot 52 - Closing Documents, 2009 (Box 149, Folder 8)
    - LSR Fund - Caneel Bay - Trigo and Klumb Option Agreements, 2008 (Box 164, Folder 8)
    - LSR - US Virgin Islands - Island Resources Foundation, 2004 (Box 165, Folder 10)
    - Virgin Islands National Park - Publications, 1970s (Box 302, Folder 3)
  - Welfare, 2006; 3_11
    - Welfare - The Thompson Center, 2006 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Woodstock, 1948-2009; 3_12
    - Billings Farm and Museum - General, 1996-2003 (Box 2, Folder 5-7)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Budgets, 1993-1997 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Cambridge Associates Study, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 9, Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Farm Operations, 1998-1991 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Billings Farm and Museum: In Review - 1999 Visitor Center Opening, Woodstock, Vermont, 1999-2000 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Lease, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Long-Range Plan, Executive Summary, 1988 June 28 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Newspaper Clippings and Calendar Events, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Portland Bangor Waste Oil (PBWO), Wells Settlement Fund (Billings Dairy Environmental Claim), 2000-2002 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Selected Television Features - 2001 Season, VHS (Box T1)
      Open for research. Access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Twentieth-Anniversary Celebration, 2003 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Par - General, 1993-1996 (Box 37, Folder 15)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Opening Ceremony - Speeches and Remarks, 1998 June 5 (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Conservation Stewardship Workshop, 1993 November 19-21 (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan, 1995 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Report of the Historic Forest Planning Charrette, 2000 November 3-5 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - Bourne Trust, 1995-1998 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller NHP - Opening Ceremony - General, 1998 June 5-6 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller NHP - Opening Ceremony - Film, 1998 June 5-6 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller NHP - Opening Ceremony - Open House, 1998 June 5-6 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - LSR - Valley News Articles, 1983 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - General, 1990-1999 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock Foundation - General, 1994-2000 (Box 57, Folder 1-2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - General, 2001-2002 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 1999 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 5-6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 2001 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 2002 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 2003 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Board of Directors and Board of Trustees - Annual Meetings - Minutes, 1993-1999 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Executive Committee, 1992-2000 (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Billings, Richard - Mansion - Lease, 1993 (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Coolidge Film, 1989-1996 (Box 56, Folder 12-13)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Coolidge Film, 1997-2004 (Box 59, Folder 3-5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Financials, 1995-2004; 10 files (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Guggenheim Film - Contract, 1995-1998 (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Guggenheim Film - Award Nominations, 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Lease Agreement - Martin House, 1998 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Maintenance Fund, 1998-2004 (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Foundation - NPS/USFS Conservation History Project, 1999-2000 (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Portfolio - General, 1998-2004 (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Projects - Speaking of the Future, "A Dialogue on Conservation", 2003 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - MBRNHP - Thomas, Roy, 1998-2002 (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Construction, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Exhibit Script and Photo Selections, 1999 (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Opening Events - General, 1999 July 11-12 (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Opening Events - Public Relations, 1999 July 11-12 (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Vlaminck Painting, 1990-2000 (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Sale of Indian Baskets, 1994-2000 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Eagle Properties, Inc. - General, 1993-2000 (Box 60, Folder 9-10)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Eagle Properties Inc. - Budget, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Echo Acre - General, 1995-2005 (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Echo Acre - Sales Contract, 2005 (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Echo Acres - Gully Road - Appraisals, 2004 (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Echo Acres - Hitchcock Property, 1992-2002 (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Echo Acres - Mertens House, 1989-2000 (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - French Property, 1988-1997 (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - LSR/WRC Management Agreement, 1992-1995 (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Property Surveys, 1977-1995 (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Woodrock, 1995-2000 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      Contains Woodstock original prices.
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General, 1997-2001 (Box 61, Folder 11-12)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Carriage Barn - Opening Ceremony, 1999 August 7 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - Cash Requirements, 1996-2005 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Deed of Gift and Pledge Letter - LSR, 1992 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Donation of Tangibles - LSR and MFR, 1997 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Film Project - General, 1994-1999 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Film Project - LSR Interview, 1996-1997 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Film Project - Script, 1996-1998 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - General, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 8-10)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - General, 1994-1997 (Box 63, Folder 1-5)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - Environmental Impact Statement, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - Funding, 1992-1993 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - Publicity and Public Relations, 1992-1998 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General Management Plan - Winks Proposal, 1994 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Guggenheim Film - Photo Research, 1996-1997 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Library of Congress, 1993-1994 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - NPS Letter - Payment in Lieu of Taxes, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - General, 1991-1997 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Public Forum - Remarks, 1991 August 12 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Senate Appropriations, 1994-2000 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Stewardship Initiative - Conservation Study Institute - General, 1994-2002 (Box 64, Folder 4-5)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Tax Fund, 1991-1999 (Box 64, Folder 6-7)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - General, 1996-1997 (Box 64, Folder 8-9)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - General, 1998-2003 (Box 65, Folder 1-6)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Appraisal Report, 1998 June 25 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Financials, 1991-2000 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Expansion - Financial, 1988-1990 (Box 65, Folder 9-10)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Budgets, 1998-2002 (Box 66, Folder 1-4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Budgets, 2003-2005; 1996 (Box 67, Folder 1-3)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Capital Requests, 2000-2002 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Clement vs. Woodstock Resort Corporation, 1995 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Economic Study and Appraisal - Country Club and Sports Center, 1998 September 1 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - General, 2000-2005 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - Moon Garage, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - Mt. Pet, 2003 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Real Estate - Mt. Tom, 2005 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Service Mark Applications, 2002-2003 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Spa Research, 1999-2000 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Historical Society - General, 1988-2004 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock Historical Society - One and Five the Green Properties, 2000-2002 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Property - Woodstock - General (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - Property - Woodstock - Marsh Billings Rockefeller National Historic Park (MBRNHP), 1992-1999 (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Jackson Lake Lodge Dedication, 1955 June 11 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock School Fund, 2000-2003 (Box 89, Folder 5)
    - Land and Water Conservation Fund - General, 1999-2004 (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - General, 2003-2006 (Box 91, Folder 2-3)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Guggenheim Productions - "A Place in the Land" - Final Transcript, 2006 (Box 91, Folder 4)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Hitchcock Right of First Refusal, 2000-2001 (Box 91, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Partnership Issues, 2002-2004 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Vermont Community Foundation, 1987-2008 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Wyndham Foundation - General, 2001-2003 (Box 91, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - LSR Properties - Carriage Collection, 1994-1996 (Box 91, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Cash Requirements, 2004-2007 (Box 91, Folder 10-11)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Cultural Landscape Report, 2001-2003 (Box 91, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Conservation Stewardship Workshop, 1993 November (Box 91, Folder 13)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Marketing, 2000-2007 (Box 92, Folder 2-5)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Public Relations, 2006 (Box 92, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - General, 2004-2005 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - Marsh-Billings Mansion - Mary French Rockefeller (MFR) - Tangible Property - Appraisal, 1997 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Billings Farm and Museum - Scrapbook, 1999-2000 (Box 100, Folder 2)
      Primarily photos and articles re: the opening ceremony for the Marsh-Billings Farm and Museum Visitor Center.
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Senate Hearings Report, 1992 March 26 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Senate Hearings Report, 1992 June 2 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Report, 2000-2001 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - General, 1997-2008 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Visitor Center - Act 250, 1997-1998 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Woodstock Resort Corporation - Planning, 2000-2001 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Woodstock - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Brochures, 1999 (Box 101, Folder 4)
      Brochures for the Stewardship Initiative and the Conservation Study Institute.
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Art, 1991 (Box 101, Folder 17)
      Appraisals of Chinese art and porcelain.
    - Marsh-Billings-Rockefeller National Historical Park - Department of Interior - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Woodstock Foundation - Civil War Book Project, 2005 (Box 110, Folder 5)
    - Woodstock - Mansion - General, 1995-2001 (Box 117, Folder 6)
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Appraisal, 1991-1997 (Box 117, Folder 7)
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Appraisal - Contents, 1990s (Box 117, Folder 8)
    - Woodstock - Mansion - Contents - General, 1990s (Box 117, Folder 9)
    - Woodstock - MBRNHP - General, 2002-2008 (Box 117, Folder 12)
    - Woodstock - Billings Farm and Museum - General, 2001-2005 (Box 117, Folder 13)